
> signora-frontend@0.1.0 test
> node --test

TAP version 13
# Subtest: deliberate DELETE carries the exact revision/hash body with memory-only authorization
ok 1 - deliberate DELETE carries the exact revision/hash body with memory-only authorization
  ---
  duration_ms: 147.7604
  ...
# Subtest: validation and stale-revision errors expose actionable fields and request identity
ok 2 - validation and stale-revision errors expose actionable fields and request identity
  ---
  duration_ms: 8.3063
  ...
# Subtest: reload suppresses completed versions and stores no caption or credential
ok 3 - reload suppresses completed versions and stores no caption or credential
  ---
  duration_ms: 21.5013
  ...
# Subtest: authoritative state replaces missed corrections, expired work and completed server progress
ok 4 - authoritative state replaces missed corrections, expired work and completed server progress
  ---
  duration_ms: 5.7596
  ...
# Subtest: correction updates captions but asks the player for a safe stop instead of preparing mid-identifier
ok 5 - correction updates captions but asks the player for a safe stop instead of preparing mid-identifier
  ---
  duration_ms: 18.0048
  ...
# Subtest: lost completion ACK is recovered after reload without preparing or replaying the message
ok 6 - lost completion ACK is recovered after reload without preparing or replaying the message
  ---
  duration_ms: 31.3365
  ...
# Subtest: a superseded start acknowledgement rejects its promise without invalidating the socket
ok 7 - a superseded start acknowledgement rejects its promise without invalidating the socket
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.0875
  ...
# Subtest: development live plans play review clips with a fresh display lease and no fabricated review
ok 8 - development live plans play review clips with a fresh display lease and no fabricated review
  ---
  duration_ms: 41.2655
  ...
# Subtest: live priority interruption cannot split a five-clip identifier
ok 9 - live priority interruption cannot split a five-clip identifier
  ---
  duration_ms: 8.3044
  ...
# Subtest: a cached operational plan requires a lease before start and stops on freshness loss
ok 10 - a cached operational plan requires a lease before start and stops on freshness loss
  ---
  duration_ms: 7.3176
  ...
# Subtest: reviewed announcement plan preserves atomic identifier groups and rejects altered contracts
ok 11 - reviewed announcement plan preserves atomic identifier groups and rejects altered contracts
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.3506
  ...
# Subtest: 1 repeated occurrences finish in exact order on one avatar
ok 12 - 1 repeated occurrences finish in exact order on one avatar
  ---
  duration_ms: 7.426
  ...
# Subtest: 3 repeated occurrences finish in exact order on one avatar
ok 13 - 3 repeated occurrences finish in exact order on one avatar
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.9218
  ...
# Subtest: 12 repeated occurrences finish in exact order on one avatar
ok 14 - 12 repeated occurrences finish in exact order on one avatar
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.6785
  ...
# Subtest: no first sign is visible when any required clip fails preload
ok 15 - no first sign is visible when any required clip fails preload
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.7226
  ...
# Subtest: server invalidation blocks a fully cached plan before playback
ok 16 - server invalidation blocks a fully cached plan before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.4515
  ...
# Subtest: late preload completion cannot overwrite a newer queue
ok 17 - late preload completion cannot overwrite a newer queue
  ---
  duration_ms: 51.6794
  ...
# Subtest: cancel during start authorization prevents stale playback
ok 18 - cancel during start authorization prevents stale playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.0845
  ...
# Subtest: expiry is enforced while ready and during playback
ok 19 - expiry is enforced while ready and during playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.8499
  ...
# Subtest: caller mutation cannot change the prepared ordered snapshot
ok 20 - caller mutation cannot change the prepared ordered snapshot
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.9407
  ...
# Subtest: a new plan cannot inherit an omitted animated channel from the preceding sign
ok 21 - a new plan cannot inherit an omitted animated channel from the preceding sign
  ---
  duration_ms: 5.1569
  ...
# Subtest: manifest rejects external asset URL
ok 22 - manifest rejects external asset URL
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3793
  ...
# Subtest: manifest rejects partial readiness
ok 23 - manifest rejects partial readiness
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.6668
  ...
# Subtest: manifest rejects operational composition
ok 24 - manifest rejects operational composition
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3127
  ...
# Subtest: manifest rejects invented blend
ok 25 - manifest rejects invented blend
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3441
  ...
# Subtest: manifest rejects lost occurrence
ok 26 - manifest rejects lost occurrence
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3876
  ...
# Subtest: asset reader verifies actual streamed bytes and never sends token in the URL
ok 27 - asset reader verifies actual streamed bytes and never sends token in the URL
  ---
  duration_ms: 117.4581
  ...
# Subtest: GLB preflight rejects external resources and invalid declared length before decoding
ok 28 - GLB preflight rejects external resources and invalid declared length before decoding
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.1602
  ...
# Subtest: bounded cache retains required clips and evicts only unpinned entries
ok 29 - bounded cache retains required clips and evicts only unpinned entries
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.2312
  ...
# Subtest: shared graphics resources and image handles are released once
ok 30 - shared graphics resources and image handles are released once
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.8503
  ...
# Subtest: PCM recording encodes exact mono 16 kHz samples and clips amplitude
ok 31 - PCM recording encodes exact mono 16 kHz samples and clips amplitude
  ---
  duration_ms: 20.4613
  ...
# Subtest: Empty, short, excessive and nonfinite audio never becomes an upload
ok 32 - Empty, short, excessive and nonfinite audio never becomes an upload
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.1828
  ...
# Subtest: independent rigs compare by structure, not object identity; opposite quaternions agree
ok 33 - independent rigs compare by structure, not object identity; opposite quaternions agree
  ---
  duration_ms: 50.8429
  ...
# Subtest: matching bone names cannot hide changed parent transform
ok 34 - matching bone names cannot hide changed parent transform
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.4579
  ...
# Subtest: matching bone names cannot hide changed local transform
ok 35 - matching bone names cannot hide changed local transform
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.376
  ...
# Subtest: matching bone names cannot hide changed hierarchy
ok 36 - matching bone names cannot hide changed hierarchy
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.4999
  ...
# Subtest: matching bone names cannot hide changed inverse bind pose
ok 37 - matching bone names cannot hide changed inverse bind pose
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.9049
  ...
# Subtest: matching bone names cannot hide changed skin bind matrix
ok 38 - matching bone names cannot hide changed skin bind matrix
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.4672
  ...
# Subtest: matching bone names cannot hide changed joint order
ok 39 - matching bone names cannot hide changed joint order
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.5295
  ...
# Subtest: matching bone names cannot hide changed morph mapping
ok 40 - matching bone names cannot hide changed morph mapping
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.9637
  ...
# Subtest: duplicate or absent bone identities fail profile capture
ok 41 - duplicate or absent bone identities fail profile capture
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.2661
  ...
# Subtest: binding validates real properties including constant fingers and required morph channels
ok 42 - binding validates real properties including constant fingers and required morph channels
  ---
  duration_ms: 33.2954
  ...
# Subtest: invalid missing target fails before playback
ok 43 - invalid missing target fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.4849
  ...
# Subtest: invalid indexed target fails before playback
ok 44 - invalid indexed target fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.1623
  ...
# Subtest: invalid hierarchy target fails before playback
ok 45 - invalid hierarchy target fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.1926
  ...
# Subtest: invalid unsupported property fails before playback
ok 46 - invalid unsupported property fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.7428
  ...
# Subtest: invalid prototype property fails before playback
ok 47 - invalid prototype property fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.8328
  ...
# Subtest: invalid duplicate track fails before playback
ok 48 - invalid duplicate track fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.3658
  ...
# Subtest: invalid wrong width fails before playback
ok 49 - invalid wrong width fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.3385
  ...
# Subtest: invalid negative time fails before playback
ok 50 - invalid negative time fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.7784
  ...
# Subtest: invalid repeated time fails before playback
ok 51 - invalid repeated time fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.8946
  ...
# Subtest: invalid time outside clip fails before playback
ok 52 - invalid time outside clip fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.2203
  ...
# Subtest: invalid nonfinite time fails before playback
ok 53 - invalid nonfinite time fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.6096
  ...
# Subtest: invalid nonfinite value fails before playback
ok 54 - invalid nonfinite value fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.5917
  ...
# Subtest: invalid nonfinite duration fails before playback
ok 55 - invalid nonfinite duration fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.002
  ...
# Subtest: invalid empty clip fails before playback
ok 56 - invalid empty clip fails before playback
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0123
  ...
# Subtest: ambiguous target and unavailable required morph channel fail binding
ok 57 - ambiguous target and unavailable required morph channel fail binding
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0798
  ...
# Subtest: 1 sequential occurrences finish exactly once on the same avatar and restore it after cleanup
ok 58 - 1 sequential occurrences finish exactly once on the same avatar and restore it after cleanup
  ---
  duration_ms: 9.5404
  ...
# Subtest: 3 sequential occurrences finish exactly once on the same avatar and restore it after cleanup
ok 59 - 3 sequential occurrences finish exactly once on the same avatar and restore it after cleanup
  ---
  duration_ms: 24.6453
  ...
# Subtest: 12 sequential occurrences finish exactly once on the same avatar and restore it after cleanup
ok 60 - 12 sequential occurrences finish exactly once on the same avatar and restore it after cleanup
  ---
  duration_ms: 42.22
  ...
# Subtest: twelve repeated occurrences share one action while all twelve replay
ok 61 - twelve repeated occurrences share one action while all twelve replay
  ---
  duration_ms: 11.1756
  ...
# Subtest: a missing later clip target prevents the first occurrence from moving
ok 62 - a missing later clip target prevents the first occurrence from moving
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3169
  ...
# Subtest: invalid sampled quaternion fails and cleanup restores the original pose
ok 63 - invalid sampled quaternion fails and cleanup restores the original pose
  ---
  duration_ms: 6.4414
  ...
# Subtest: empty sequences and invalid sample steps fail immediately
ok 64 - empty sequences and invalid sample steps fail immediately
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.482
  ...
# Subtest: basic station setup preserves advanced rules and builds the exact platform inventory
ok 65 - basic station setup preserves advanced rules and builds the exact platform inventory
  ---
  duration_ms: 9.9354
  ...
# Subtest: arrival example uses actual IDs and preserves repeated identifier digits
ok 66 - arrival example uses actual IDs and preserves repeated identifier digits
  ---
  duration_ms: 9.7817
  ...
# Subtest: example refuses missing or ambiguous concepts instead of inventing IDs
ok 67 - example refuses missing or ambiguous concepts instead of inventing IDs
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.8675
  ...
1..67
# tests 67
# suites 0
# pass 67
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 1504.2916
